freshdeals.com 2012-09-20

# FreshDeals.com | Privacy Policy

#### What information do we collect?

Fresh Deals collects information from you when you sign in with Facebook, ask or answer a question, or share a deal or listing. Activity information is collected in both anonymous and personally identifiable forms - including specific questions, answers, comments, and "likes." When ordering through our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address or mailing address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

#### Unsubscribe Information

If you wish to unsubscribe from Fresh Deals emails or notifications please visit: [http://www.Fresh Deals.com/unsubscribe](http://www.freshdeals.com/unsubscribe "http://www.FreshDeals.com/unsubscribe").

**Information from other sources**

We may periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from other businesses, business partners, and other third parties and add it to our account information or other information we have collected. Examples of information that we may receive include: updated delivery and address information, purchase history, and additional demographic information.

**Information about others**

We may also collect and store personal information about other people that you provide to us. If you use our website to send others (friends, relatives, colleagues, etc.) information that may interest them or messages (such as invitations) through our system, we may store your personal information, and the personal information of each such recipient.

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website.

Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).

To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer. servicerequests and support needs)

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

To send periodic emails.

The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

All activities outside of viewing (asking, answering, liking and commenting) are assigned your Facebook name and profile picture, unless your privacy settings dictate otherwise (first name only, default Fresh Deals picture).

All questions, answers, and comments created by you can be viewed by anyone visiting the Fresh Deals site or visiting partner sites that include Fresh Deals content.

#### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information. Our physical, electronic and procedural measures help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. In addition, we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal information.

We want you to feel confident using our website to transact business. However, no system can be completely secure. Although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or other communications will always remain secure. Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their personal information and should avoid sending personal information through insecure email. Please refer to the Federal Trade Commission's website at <http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data.shtm> for information about how to protect yourself against identity theft.

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We may share your personal information with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include processing credit card payments, delivering packages, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, supporting our website functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our website. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.

#### Third Party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

#### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us.
